cinemax.co.in 2007-06-07

# Untitled Page

**INTRODUCTION  
**Your privacy is important to cinemax.co.in. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. This information helps us improve your movie going experience with better content, services and opportunities. This policy tells you about the information gathering and dissemination that we conduct. As we continue to grow, this policy may change, so please check back periodically for updates. 

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**   
We ask our users to register when they use the cinemax.co.in site and services (collectively, the "Service"). Through our online registration process, we collect a variety of information about the user, which may include, among other things, name of the person registering, location, gender, phone number, email address, user name and password. cinemax.co.in may also request and collect other information from time to time. 

We automatically track information related to use of the Service. This information may include, among other things, URL tracking information, what browser the user is using, the user's IP address, pages and ads viewed by a user and selections or other actions taken on the Service. We may track usage through cookies. A cookie is a small data file written to a user's hard drive. Cookies may be used to, among other things, allow automated log-in and may contain information such as a Login ID or other information about preferences or Internet use. Third party advertisers that we work with may also place cookies on browsers of users of our Service. 

We also collect information about your movie preferences. For example, we may collect, among other things, information such as what movies you purchase tickets to or what theatres you attend. We may save information sent or posted to the Service. For example, we may save messages posted in our chat rooms or other message areas or feedback left for other users. We may collect correspondence, such as emails or letters, sent to us. We may collect user responses to online polls, ads, surveys, electronic newsletters and questionnaires.   
**

DELETION OF INFORMATION AND RECORDS 

**   
While cinemax.co.in may track and store information, cinemax.co.in shall not be obligated to do so and may delete any information and records, in whole or in part, at any time.   
**

WHAT WE USE THE INFORMATION FOR

**  
We use the demographic information to enhance your user experience by, among other things, delivering you content that is relevant to your interests. We may use the contact information you provide us to notify you of new services or special deals that our partners or we are offering, to distribute movie related information to you or to conduct surveys or other similar activities. When you register with us, you may choose to opt-out of receiving these notices or mailings from cinemax.co.in at the time of registration. 

cinemax.co.in does not sell or rent personal information about its customers to any third parties at this time. cinemax.co.in does, however, perform statistical analyses of customer usage in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various parts of the Company's web site, and the Company may share that information with current and prospective advertisers, and other interested third parties. This information is aggregated data only (such as statistics), and contains no personally identifiable information whatsoever. 

cinemax.co.in Strives to protect the personally identifiable information of the users. 

cinemax.co.in May disclose the personally identifiable information only on:   
· Expressed authorization of the user to do so   
· The provision of the requested service demands so   
· Requirements to comply with the governing law   
· Opportunity to add value to the user   
However, cinemax.co.in may share aggregated statistical information about the use of the cinemax.co.in web site with partners and associates for the purpose of research and analysis. Even in these cases, cinemax.co.in will strive to protect the individual users' personally identifiable information. **  
**   
Please note that cinemax.co.in may sell, share or transfer personally identifiable information about its customers with any successor in interest (e.g. if the Company is sold to a third party). Additionally, in certain cases, cinemax.co.in may be required to disclose your personally identifiable information when the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation. 

cinemax.co.in users should also be aware that if they voluntarily disclose personal information in any chat areas or bulletin boards within the cinemax.co.in web site, that information might be collected and disseminated by third-parties, and result in, among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, and offers from third parties. This third-party conduct is out of the control of the Company. 

**SECURITY**   
cinemax.co.in has implemented security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We protect the secure areas of our Site with a firewall. Although cinemax.co.in has implemented adequate security measures, the site has contracted Verisign to provide an extra assurance of security. Although, the site is completely virus-free, the User is advised to employ virus scans for extra security, as cinemax.co.in is not liable for any virus picked up at the time of transmission. 

**CHOICE/OPT-OUT**   
cinemax.co.in allows users the option to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at registration. If you decide later to opt-out you can contact us by sending e-mail to info@cinemax.co.in

**GENERAL INFORMATION**   
Please note that cinemax.co.in tries its best to collect data from the most authentic source. However, at any stage, cinemax.co.in is not liable for any loss, monetary or otherwise, resulting from the usage of their data. 

**QUESTIONS**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, you can email us at   
info@cinemax.co.in
